You might be able, for example to have fun backgrounds.
You might be able to attach interesting surrounds to it.
And of course, you should always be able to upgrade the camera.
So start with a cheap camera.
And then you can always upgrade, later.
Durability is also a big feature for kids.
So go on-line, check reviews and choose a camera which is going to stand up, to some hard use.
At the beginning of course, it's probably best to choose a very simple point and shoot camera.
However, later on, you can always upgrade to a camera which has facilities such as an optical or digital zoom.
Which will have anti red eye facility.
And perhaps is got a built in macro attachment on it.
If you really have the money, you might even be able to afford image stabilization.
Lastly, don't worry too much about mega pixels.
Try to find a camera that's easier to use.
The easier it is to use, the better your child will like it.
And remember lastly, don't buy a camera that you like.
Because they will probably hate it.